and there's no more filter have you
noticed that there's no filter we had an
argument the other day and they say you
know never go to sleep angry so he gets
into bed and I'm trying to be nice and I
said I know I'm not your favorite person
and he he punched the pillow and he said
you are you are my favorite person
that's how pathetic my life is right now
and if you're married or in a
relationship you know that was a
compliment of the deepest
[Laughter]
marriage we do we're very happy marriage
I mean I know he'd like to be getting a
little more action but you know in this
economy
where are my married people clap where
are my married people clap
wow all right so you will appreciate
this so we're home and this never
happens we're watching TV and all of a
sudden I just got swept up in the moment
and I had all this passion and I did
something I can't even remember the last
time I did I made the first move are you
paying attention me I
and my husband had no idea what was
going on he was so confused
and I watched his face as he figured it
out he started to panic he was like what
did you do to the car what foreign
it was a speeding ticket but that's not
the point I'm still showing
I really know I'm very I I feel very
blessed very lucky that I found him you
know I was single for a very long time
it took a long time for me to find Mr
Right I was single way past the
expiration date
it made my parents crazy my father's
like I can't figure it out why isn't she
married look at her she's gorgeous look
at Corey she looks just like Grandma
they meant it in a good way they did
apparently when my grandmother was a
young girl she won a beauty contest yes
of course it was in Romania so I don't
know how high the bar was
and when I was young when I was in my
20s you're in your 20s let me see Hands
20s when I yes so when I was in my 20s
my grandmother gave me dating advice and
it was very funny because she had that
voice from the old country and she would
always say he vote buys the cow if the
milk is free remember that girls anybody
would know that one he vote by the cow
if the milk is free but she only wanted
me to go out with her best friend's
grandson Preston who was also her hair
colorist
finally I had to break it to her I said
Grandma Preston is lactose intolerant
[Applause]
yes
hey thanks for watching make sure you
download the dry bar app and use my
promo code you know I love promo codes
Corey kahaney tough to spell just Google
it thank you